2007 Tesla Drive, Colorado Springs, Colorado 80909 (719) 439-0595 SamanthaBernard20@gmail.com

maybe add more live spacing work (1.5) **Skills**

I am earning my Bachelors in Computer Science with a Mathematics minor in the University of Colorado Boulder Partnership program at Western Colorado University. I have a Microsoft MTA: Introduction to Programming Using Java certification, I am comfortable with C++, C, as well as introductions into Python, Scala and R. My relevant coursework includes software engineering, systems programming in C using a Linux system, multivariable calculus, and technical writing.

maybe choose yor so and talk about them a bit. **Experience** June 13, 2022 - Present

Software Engineer Intern Junior C - L3Harris Technologies

August 24, 2021 - December 16, 2021

Lambda Learning Center, Western Colorado University - Math & Computer Science Tutor January 31, 2022 - Present

Association for Computing Machinery-Women's (ACMW) Student Chapter - Chair February 17, 2021 - May, 2021

Rady Machine Shop, Western Colorado University - Teacher's Assistant

August 9, 2021 - Present

Resident's Assistant, Western Colorado University - Residence Life

September 14, 2021 - Present

Promotions Manager, DJ and Announcer for KWSB 91.1 FM local radio

June 3, 2021 - July 17, 2021

Merchandise Services Team, Lowe's Home Improvement - Plant Caretaker

September 21, 2018 - July 11, 2019

Muse Comics + **Games** - *Part-time employee*

August, 2016 - June 2020

Leadership and Membership, FIRST Robotics Competition Team 2996, Cougars Gone Wired

maybe flip date and title. maybe personal preference though **Education** 7 2020-2024

↓ Earning Bachelor of Science in Computer Science - Western Colorado University

oldect

Certified Microsoft MTA: Introduction to Programming Using Java

2020

High School Diploma From Coronado High School, Colorado Springs

2018

HAM Radio Technician's License, call sign WXØ-BAT

2019

Rotary Youth Leadership Awards Summer Camp (RYLA) - Attendee

1 Western Way, C.P.O. # 5033, Gunnison, CO 81231 (719) 439-0595 SamanthaBernard20@gmail.com

Skills

I am earning my Bachelors in Computer Science in the University of Colorado Boulder Partnership and Honors programs at Western Colorado University. I am passionate and high energy, I love working in teams. I have experience with Google and Microsoft products. I have excelled in economics and technical writing courses and appreciate positions with careful attention to detail. Through my positions working with people and customers, I have fantastic interpersonal and communication skills.

Experience

August 9, 2021 - Present

Resident's Assistant, Western Colorado University - Residence Life

In this position, I have worked with my supervisors and administration of the university to build and execute curriculum; ensure policy was fairly enforced, and helped foster interpersonal relationships with my residents and between residents on my floor. I handled paperwork for any breaches in policy I reported and communicated with Gunnison Police Department, Gunnison Fire Department, EMTs and Campus Security on several occasions to ensure student's safety and the security of the complex.

August 24, 2021 - December 16, 2021

Lambda Learning Center, Western Colorado University - Math & Computer Science Tutor

At the tutoring center, we had weekly meetings to prepare for possible content questions students may have; during shifts, I was always ready for anything. The tutoring center was run on an open door policy, so I was prepared to field any question a student may have for math and computer science. While on shift, I was in charge of hourly checks and various paperwork to keep the center clean and running smoothly.

September 14, 2021 - Present

Promotions Manager, DJ and Announcer for KWSB 91.1 FM local radio - Weekly 1 hour show

For KWSB I: planned, budgeted and coordinated events; recruited new DJs; oversaw the physical and digital promotions for the station; and worked directly with other managers and DJs to ensure the success of these measures.

June 3, 2021 - July 17, 2021

Merchandise Services Team, Lowe's Home Improvement - Plant Waterer

In this position, I ensured the health of plants in the arboretum, helped receive deliveries and set up displays, assisted customers in finding answers to their questions, and ensured the cleanliness and safety of the nursery.

February 17, 2021 - May, 2021

Rady Machine Shop, Western Colorado University - Teacher's Assistant

For my work in the Machine Shop, I ensured the shop was clean and safe, assisted in the creation of processes for checking out tools and ensuring their return. When university tours came through the shop, I would assist in communications about the facility.

September 21, 2018 - July 11, 2019

hlovee

Muse Comics + **Games** - *Part-time employee*

January 31, 2022 - Present

Association for Computing Machinery-Women's (ACMW) Student Chapter - Chair

August, 2016 - June 2020

Leadership and Membership, FIRST Robotics Competition Team 2996, Cougars Gone Wired



- Chief Financial Officer, Vice President of Finance (2019-2020) Communicated with sponsors, created a financial plan, coordinated end-of-year celebration dinner, managed Vice Presidents in the business department of the team.
- Vice President of Outreach (2018-2019) Creating and running curriculum about simple machines for students of varying age and capabilities; organizing demonstrations in the community ranging from festivals to summer camps.
- MAD Summer Camp Organizer, Counselor (2017-2020) Created and taught a 1 week long STEM based summer camp for 6-8th graders, organized volunteers, ran advertising and collected payments.

Education

2020-2024

Earning Bachelor of Science in Computer Science - Western Colorado University

2020

High School Diploma From Coronado High School, Colorado Springs

2019

Certified Microsoft MTA: Introduction to Programming Using Java

2019

Rotary Youth Leadership Awards Summer Camp (RYLA) - Attendee

I was competitively selected by my local Rotary chapter to attend and chosen by camp leaders to speak at closing ceremonies.

2018

HAM Radio Technician's License, call sign WXØ-BAT

HAM Radio licenses allow amateur radio operators access to certain frequencies under jurisdiction of the FCC.